Now that we learned how to actually do this trigger,
我们已经学习了如何执行触发
let's write the function that gets executed after this returns true.
现在让我们来写一下这里返回 true 之后要用到的启动函数
This is going to be our perform upkeep function,
也就是所谓的 "performUpkeep" 函数
which we can see an example again in the chainlink documentation.
我们同样可以在 Chainlink 文档中找到它的例子
Now when it's time to pick a random winner,
当要开始遴选随机优胜者时
actually, what we're going to do is just we're just going to call this request random winner function.
我们实际上要做的就是调用这个 "requestRandomWinner" 函数
So instead of having this extra function,
所以我们不需要创建额外的函数
let's just transform our request random winner function into this perform upkeep.
而是直接把 "requestRandomWinner" 函数改成 "performUpkeep"
Since once check upkeep returns true, the chain link nodes will automatically call this perform upkeep function.
一旦 "checkUpkeep" 返回了 true，Chainlink 节点就会自动调用这个 "performUpkeep" 函数
So in function request random winner, let's rename this to perform upkeep.
所以我们要把 "requestRandomWinner" 重新命名为 "performUpkeep"
And we'll have it take the input parameter bytes called Data perform data
并且我们要让它获取相应的输入参数 "bytes calldata /* performData */"
bytes, called data, perform data.
`bytes calldata /* performData */`
In our checkup, keep we had to perform data,
如果我们的 "checkUpkeep" 中存在 "performData"
we would automatically pass it to our performance keep,
我们就会自动将其传入我们的 "performUpkeep"
we're not going to pass anything to perform upkeep, we can leave it commented out like this.
我们并不会给 "performUpkeep" 传入任何内容，直接把它注释掉就行了，就像这样
Since perform upkeep is actually identified in the keeper compatible interface,
由于 "performUpkeep" 实际上是在 "KeeperCompatibleInterface" 中识别的
this is now going to have to override that function.
这样做实际上会重写这个函数
Now we want to do a little bit of validation before we continue here.
在继续之前，我们打算做一点小小的验证
Because right now anybody can call our perform upkeep function.
因为现在任何人都可以调用我们的 "performUpkeep" 函数
So we want to make sure that it only gets called when checkup keep is true.
我们要确保它只会在 "checkUpkeep" 返回 true 时才会被调用
An easy way for us to do that is to actually call our own checkup, keep function.
要想达到这一点，一个简单的方法就是调用我们的 "checkUpkeep" 函数
Now right now, checkup keep it's an external. So we actually can't call our own checkup keep function.
现在 "checkUpkeep" 是一个 external，所以我们自己还无法调用 "checkUpkeep" 函数
So let's change it to public so that even our own smart contracts can call this checkup keep function.
让我们把它改成 public 这样即使是我们自己的智能合约也可以调用这个 "checkUpkeep"
Now that we've made it public in perform upkeep, we can call checkup, keep passing nothing,
现在我们把 "performUpkeep" 变成 public 的，然后就可以不传入任何参数调用 "checkUpkeep"
and then return the upkeep needed and perform data which we don't really care about.
并返回 "upkeepNeeded" 以及我们并不关心的 "performData"
So we'll get we'll get that ball up keep needed. And then we don't care about perform data.
所以我们获取这个 `bool upkeepNeeded` 然后，我们并不关心 "performData"
So we'll leave that blank equals check up keep. And we'll pass it a blank called data.
所以我们把这里留白，然后 `= checkUpkeep` 传入一个空白的 "calldata"
Now, we want to make sure that this is true in order to keep going with the function.
现在，我们想在这个为 true 的时候继续运行函数
So we could write a require here, but we're going to do if not up keep needed,
我们可以写 "require" 但我们要用 `if(!upkeepNeeded)`
then we're going to revert with a new error that we create raffle. upkeep not needed.
然后我们 `revert` 一个新的错误类型 `Raffle__UpkeepNotNeeded`
And we're going to pass some variables to this error so that
我们要给这个报错传入某些变量
whoever was running into this bug can hopefully see why they're getting this error.
这样无论是谁运行出这个 bug 都可以看到为什么会收到这个报错
So we'll pass the balance of this contract just in case there's no ether in here.
所以我们传入这个合约的余额，以没有以太币
We'll add the players dot length, just in case there's no players.
然后添加 `players.length`，以防没有玩家
And we'll add a un 256 s underscore raffle state.
再添加 `uint256(s_raffleState)
Make sure that the raffles actually open.
确保抽奖状态为开放
And then of course, we'll need to create this air at the top
当然了，我们还需要在顶部把这个错误创建出来
air, raffle upkeep not needed, which is going to take a un 256 current balance un 256 non players and you went to fit six raffle state.
`error Raffle__UpkeepNotNeeded(uint256 currentBalance, uint256 numPlayers, uint256 raffleState)
Our code is starting to look really professional. This is awesome.
我们的代码看起来真是越来越专业了
Now something that we forgot to do back in the fulfill random words because we actually forgot to reset timestamp
我们还忘做了某件事，回到 "fulfillRandomWords"，我们忘记重置时间戳了
every time a winner is picked. We want to reset the timestamp as well
每当选出一个优胜者，我们就要重置一下时间戳
so that we can wait another interval and let people participate in the lottery for that interval.
这样我们才能开启下一个间隔，并让人们能在这段时间里加入到抽奖中来
So we'll scroll down into fulfill random words.
所以我们拉到下面，到 "fulfillRandomWords" 里
And right after we reset players will also reset the timestamp.
在重置 "players" 之后，我们同样重置时间戳
Okay great and I think we're just about done here.
非常好，我想我们已经完成这一部分了